<resources>
    <string name="app_name">project_2</string>
    <string name="plant_plus">Plant Plus</string>
    <string name="todo">flower</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="emailToast">You must enter email to register!</string>
    <string name="Marigold">Marigold health benefits:
Soothes skin and treats skin diseases
Reduces inflammation
Strong antibacterial and antiseptic properties
Treats ear pain and infection
Strengthens eyes</string>
    <string name="Catnip">
    Catnip is a fun plant for cats. Most cats are attracted to the plant and will
    roll around near it since its aroma acts as a stimulant. These medicinal plants also act as a
    sedative for cats if consumed. For humans, on the other hand, it is normally used as a stress reliever,
    sleep aid and a solution for skin issues. The majority of its health benefits come from the presence of nepetalactone,
    thymol and other compounds that make this plant great for you and your furry friend.

Catnip health benefits:
1.Repels bugs and relieves irritation from bug bites.
2.Calms restlessness, anxiety and stress.
3.Relieves stomach discomfort.
4.Accelerates recovery from colds and fevers.</string>
    <string name="Gingko">
        As one of the oldest tree species, gingko is also one of the oldest homeopathic plants and a
        key herb in Chinese medicine. The leaves are used to create capsules, tablets, and extracts,
        and when dried, can be consumed as a tea.

    It’s perhaps best-known for its ability to boost brain health. Studies say that gingko can treat
        patients with mild to moderate dementiaTrusted Source, and can slow cognition decline in
        dementia and Alzheimer’s disease.

    Recent research is looking into a component that can help diabetes,
        and there continue to be more studies, including an animal study
        that says it might influence bone healing.
    </string>
    <string name="Turmeric">
       <b> Turmeric could be beneficial for:</b>
pain caused by inflammatory diseases, like arthritis.
preventing cancer.
stopping DNA mutations.
several skin diseases.
    </string>

    <string name="Moonflowers">
       <b> INTERESTING FACT</b>
Evening primrose flowers are also called moonflower
        because they bloom as the sun begins to set. People often say they smell like lemons.
    </string>
</resources>